<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Myra Stone</title>
    <link>https://myrastone0.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Myra Stone</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2020 Designed by [Themefisher](https://themefisher.com) &amp; Developed by [Gethugothemes](https://gethugothemes.com)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://myrastone0.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>NBA Box Scores: Data Cleaning with Pandas (Part 2 of?)</title>
      <link>https://myrastone0.github.io/blog/nba_data_cleaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://myrastone0.github.io/blog/nba_data_cleaning/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll use Pandas to clean the 2018-2019 Regular Season NBA Team Box Score data scraped from ESPN.com. The web scraping code can be found here and the CSV file of the raw data can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NBA Team Box Scores (Part 1 of ?): Web Scraping with BeautifulSoup</title>
      <link>https://myrastone0.github.io/blog/nba_web_scrape/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://myrastone0.github.io/blog/nba_web_scrape/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This project uses Python and BeautifulSoup to scrape ESPN for the box scores of regular season games for NBA teams. The box score is a selected set of statistics which summarize the results of a game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searching for Galactic Winds</title>
      <link>https://myrastone0.github.io/blog/fir_gws/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://myrastone0.github.io/blog/fir_gws/</guid>
      <description>Galactic-scale outflows (or winds) are powered by stellar and/or supermassive black-hole (SMBH) accretion processes which inject energy and momentum into the interstellar medium (ISM). On a grand scale, winds may significantly affect the assembly and evolution of galaxies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iris Classification</title>
      <link>https://myrastone0.github.io/blog/iris_classification/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://myrastone0.github.io/blog/iris_classification/</guid>
      <description>Using a data set from Kaggle, build a classifier to determine an iris species based on petal and sepal characteristics.
 Problem Definition  Aim Feature Values (independent variables) Target Values (dependent variables) Inputs (the entire data set or a subset of it) Outputs (prediciton, classification)   Exploratory Data Analysis  Data Overview Visualization Data Preprocessing Data Cleaning   Model Deployment  Training the model(s)    Classify iris flowers as one of three species by using measurements of sepal length/width and petal length/width.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>